[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 4, "question": "Do you have had your heart broken?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 5, "answer": "Many times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "How do you feel about being a prime time exclusive, Harry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "If it's with you, I'm quite happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", ",", "DT", "VBP", ":", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "Do you like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "That's a big -- that's a big compliment, because when you're chilling out by the pool and you want to put some music on, those are -- those are big decisions you -- you know, I feel very honored that you picked me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "You do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "What's the matter with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "It's kind of -- I guess it's fast if I drive it fast.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "But what could you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I've spoken to him a lot about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "But you've been through that terrible pain and grief when you were very young, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Yes, I have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "It must feel strange to you, so long?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "What feels amazing to me is how the city has not only rebuilt, but taken the devastation and found opportunity.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "When you see other weather-related disasters, most recently Oklahoma and going back to Joplin and the hurricanes, tornadoes, Hurricane Sandy here in -- on the East Coast, do you think that America, as a result of what happened in Katrina and all the controversy that came out, has America got better at dealing with the immediate aftermath of these things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJS", "RB", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "ONNICK: And the America I know is the America that showed up and helped us build 80 houses for our musicians' village.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joplin"], "LOCATION": ["Oklahoma", "East Coast", "America", "Katrina", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Is it too late?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "I'd better look at my notes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Now, come on, what should every man know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Well, the song says --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "What do I need to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "In many case, it -- I married my best friend.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", ":"], "qSentId": 173, "question": "Do they even know what a CD is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "My --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NNP", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "They'd be like, dad, what -- what the hell is that piece of archaic old material?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "WP", ":", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "I'm telling you, you know, thank God there are different ways to get music out there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "But is this a -- a generic song about love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Is this you in an earlier incarnation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Did you have your heart broken?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Many times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "It's a horrible feeling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Do you sing to her in the bath?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "I try.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Wait, wait, who -- who's in the bath, me or her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NN", ",", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "You know what happens?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "ORGAN: (INAUDIBLE).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 227, "question": "How do you feel if one of your girls said, dad, I've decided I'm going to be a pop star?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Well, I don't know if you can decide to be a pop star, but if they said, dad, I'm going --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "You wouldn't mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "No, no, no, I wouldn't mind at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Do you care how much the government goes around your phone calls, emails?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "Yes, I don't want them rootling around in my gear, mate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Russell, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "Today, I'm in a very good mood.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Why are you in a good mood?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Well, I like coming on the program --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"]}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "The fact it's Friday?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "I love -- I enjoyed Friday and all of its sacred implications and I'm very happy to be with you, of course, across this prospect piece of wonderment, this geometrical division.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "But what -- what's your take on it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "I think as an immigrant in this country, a good degree of caution is advised with these matters, as you yourself have experienced from your own outspoken views.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Are they heroes, though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "That's the definition of hero, is sacrificing yourself for others.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "Is that heroic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Because, you know, like I'm not a politician or anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "ORGAN: Do you care how much a government rootles around your phone calls, e-mails?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Yes, I don't want them rootling around in my gear, mate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "But do you care?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Yes, I do, as a matter of fact.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Because that's what it comes down to, how far are you prepared to let a government do that kind of thing in the name of protecting you and keeping your country safer from potential attacks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", ",", "WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "I think that we have to test the veracity of their intention to protect before handing over such enormous power.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "I want to come back and ask the question that most of my viewers are asking every time you come on, where did you learn all these long words?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "All right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", ":", "NN", ":", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "What was it like kissing Alec Baldwin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "It's all right (ph), because he's ever so -- he's got big strong, alpha tendencies and he was very wise.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alec Baldwin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Where did you learn to speak like this, seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Listen, in --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["BBC"]}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "Where did you learn to speak like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "RAND: Like, I like reading -- I like watching BBC comedies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":"], "qSentId": 386, "question": "But when you were a young kid, you couldn't have been like seven or eight speaking like this, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "No --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Yes, I went to a comprehensive school, that school at 15, didn't I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "But did you study dictionaries?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "How is your love life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "It's about all right, thank you very much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Yes, blooming?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Blooming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Why would she use that analogy, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 484, "question": "-- much are you going to go on about this (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "I'm going to show you a picture of your ex --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Why would you do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "-- cavorting --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Earth"]}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "VBN", "NN", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "What is The Messiah Complex?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "The Messiah Complex is a disorder where the sufferer believes himself to be God's anointed chosen one on Earth to bring about, you know, peace or whatever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Yes, it's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "And who are the kind of people that you're going to be talking about in relation to the -- the kind of godlike figures?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Yes, because I'm not accusing these people of having the messiah complex, I just like that pun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alec Baldwin", "Helen Mirren", "Jason Segel"]}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "What is the great love for Russell Brand, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "It's nice to do a movie if you're with Alec Baldwin or Helen Mirren or Jonah Hill or Jason Segel.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Russell Brand"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "What is the -- what is the path to happiness for Russell Brand, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "RAND: For me, I think it's about trying to overcome relentless egotism and selfishness.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Russell Brand"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "What's the secret?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "There's really no secret.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Punishing, grueling gym sessions like I have to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", ",", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "No, but I wish I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kentucky"]}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "Why dreaming?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "Well, you know, especially as a kid growing up in Kentucky, there's a lot to, in my mind, to dream about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Johnny Bench"]}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "When you were that 18-year-old Billy Ray, what was the big dream?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Well, when I was 18 years old, the big dream for me was to be Johnny Bench.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Billy Ray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "So what do you feel about Justin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "I -- I like him, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Justin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Miley"]}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "POS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJR", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VB", "CC", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "When that happened, did you sit down with her and give her the life lesson about this is what's going to happen and these are the pitfalls?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CC", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "You know what, I think it was more met with Miley growing up under the circus tent of my life, realizing that, again, that's, you know, for -- in this business, the higher you go, the further you fall, knowing that in entertainment, you -- that's the -- there's a good side of it, that anything you can dream, you can be, have or do and it can go really, really high.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", ",", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "What was the toughest moment when you look back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "Looking back at my life, some of the adversities I faced as a kid, to be honest, early on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 629, "question": "But where go you get that from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130614pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Your parents or?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "Thank you very much for saying that and it was an honor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]